(Leonard:)What did you do?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
(Howard:)Huh. I just got called
into Human Resources.
(Penny:)Why?
I don't know. Heh.
(Raj:)Huh. That is so strange. Human Resources
wants to talk to me tomorrow.
(Raj:)Could you stop licking your ass
for two minutes? I have a problem here.
(Howard:)Do you really think
you should be drinking right now?
(Raj:)How else am I supposed to talk
to the human resources lady?
(Howard:)I don't know, seek professional help?
(Raj:)I did. The guy at the liquor store said
this stuff tastes great in coffee.
(Howard:)You got called in too? What is going on?
(Leonard:)Sheldon threw us all under the bus.
(Raj:)I feel like I've been called
to the principal's office.
(Raj:)Although I wouldn't mind
if Brown Sugar suspended me...